export default {

  difficulty1: [
    {
      question: 'Which of these is an adverb?',
      response1: 'Mean',
      response2: 'Median',
      response3: 'Across',
      response4: 'Meanwhile',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: "What is the plural form of the word 'goose'?",
      response1: 'geese',
      response2: 'gouse',
      response3: 'gooses',
      response4: 'geeses',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '10',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'In grammar, what is the name of a word that modifies a noun?',
      response1: 'Adverb',
      response2: 'Adjective',
      response3: 'Verb',
      response4: 'Article',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'What is the most common type of rhyme in English poetry?',
      response1: 'Internal rhyme',
      response2: 'Beginning rhyme',
      response3: 'End rhyme',
      response4: 'Slant rhyme',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'In grammar, what is the use of spacing, conventional signs,\nand typographical devices called?',
      response1: 'Direct Speech',
      response2: 'Punctuation',
      response3: 'Phrase',
      response4: 'Intensifer',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '1',
    },
  ],

  difficulty2: [
    {
      question: 'In grammar, which verb reflects the speakerâ€™s view towards the character of an event?',
      response1: 'Style',
      response2: 'Plot',
      response3: 'Setting',
      response4: 'Mood',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'In which figure of speech does a speaker directly address a single person or thing?',
      response1: 'Dystopia',
      response2: 'Apostrophe',
      response3: 'Farce',
      response4: 'Juxtaposition',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'What is the smallest grammatical unit of speech?',
      response1: 'Morpheme',
      response2: 'Word',
      response3: 'Form',
      response4: 'Setence',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'What is the study of language and culture called?',
      response1: 'Cultural anthropology',
      response2: 'Ethnolinguistics',
      response3: 'Phonology',
      response4: 'Social dialectology',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: "Who wrote the book 'About Analogy'?",
      response1: 'Bernard de Chartres',
      response2: 'Pindar',
      response3: 'Aristophanes of byzantium',
      response4: 'Berthold Delbruck',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },
  ],

  difficulty3: [
    {
      question: 'What is a word or a group of words that is self-contradicting called?',
      response1: 'Synecdoche',
      response2: 'Litotes',
      response3: 'Oxymoron',
      response4: 'Antithesis',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: `What was the name of the artificial language constructed in 1928 by 
            the Danish philologist Otto Jespersen?`,
      response1: 'Ido',
      response2: 'Volapuk',
      response3: 'Guosa',
      response4: 'Novial',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '20',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: 'Which of the following works was written by Charles Dickens?',
      response1: 'Animal Farm',
      response2: 'Ulysses',
      response3: 'Tale of Two Cities',
      response4: 'Dubliners',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: "Who is the author of the book 'The Lord Of The Flies'?",
      response1: 'Lois Lowry',
      response2: 'William Golding',
      response3: 'George Orwell',
      response4: 'Charles Dickens',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: 'What was the pseudonym used by the writer Louisa May Alcott?',
      response1: 'A. N. Roquelaure',
      response2: 'George Eliot',
      response3: 'Mary Berwick',
      response4: 'A. M. Barnard',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },
  ],
};
